<resources>
    <string name="app_name">splash</string>
    <string name="title_activity_login">Login</string>
    <string name="title_activity_log_in">Log_in</string>
    <string name="search">Search</string>
    <string name="messages">Messages</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <!-- Preference Titles -->
    <string name="messages_header">Messages</string>
    <string name="sync_header">Sync</string>

    <!-- Messages Preferences -->
    <string name="signature_title">Your signature</string>
    <string name="reply_title">Default reply action</string>

    <!-- Sync Preferences -->
    <string name="sync_title">Sync email periodically</string>
    <string name="attachment_title">Download incoming attachments</string>
    <string name="attachment_summary_on">Automatically download attachments for incoming emails
    </string>
    <string name="attachment_summary_off">Only download attachments when manually requested</string>
    <string name="hi_i_m_the_sender">fjlksjdflkjasdkfljaklfjslkdafjlkdasfjlksdaj jfsdjflslkdfjksldjfasd\nsadf\'sadlfjsldlkajfkljdslakfjsafsadf\nsdfsdjfsjdflksjdfi jkdgijgiergna rgdsdgdf ga\ndaf gdfgrugjfd gfgnlkfdngjfds fkdgjsodjgdfnb hfg\ndf gfdgkjdfoigr\'ds\ngj f\nfsglkfdjglkjdfgrjfdsgjhjse\ndf sglskdfjlsjgierjgsdpreijgireaogaen\'\n£$rljeojgidglfdjhsd\'\nfdsg\njfdsgjdsflkgoidshgergijgfdsg\ndsfgherohgrlgfdlkjfdlgjrgier43grlgjidjgergfdnergndsn;sergnrhjealkjregjsg\ndglkjdfgerignfdngeroijggfdngslfjdigjlslsrjgreos\ngdsjfgrjeoijghdegjfdlgjiresljfdjgirgjdrldsfg fdgjdf\nfdgkldfs\ne\ngfdfjdlkgjdlkgjldkjgldjfgljglkjfdljgfidjgfdjgfdjglrid</string>
    <string name="terms_and_conditions"><h1>Terms And Conditions</h1></string>
    <string name="condition"><b>1</b>. Acceptance of Terms By downloading, installing, or using our text messaging app , you agree to abide by these terms and conditions. If you do not agree with any part of these terms, you should not use the App. \n <b>2</b>. User Obligations You agree to use the App responsibly and lawfully. You will not use the App for any illegal or unauthorized purposes. You are responsible for the content you send through the App and must ensure it complies with applicable laws and regulations. \n <b>3</b>. App Availability and Updates We strive to provide a reliable and uninterrupted App experience. However, we do not guarantee continuous availability of the App and reserve the right to modify, suspend, or terminate the App at any time without prior notice. We may also release updates or new versions of the App, which you may be required to install for continued use. \n <b>4</b>. Privacy and Data Protection We respect your privacy and handle your personal information in accordance with our Privacy Policy. By using the App, you consent to the collection, storage, and processing of your personal data as outlined in the Privacy Policy. \n <b>5</b>. Intellectual Property The App and its associated content, including but not limited to logos, trademarks, text, images, and software, are protected by intellectual property rights. You may not copy, modify, distribute, or reproduce any part of the App without our explicit permission. \n <b>6</b>. Limitation of Liability We strive to provide a high-quality App, but we do not guarantee its accuracy, reliability, or suitability for your specific needs. We shall not be liable for any direct, indirect, incidental, or consequential damages arising from your use of the App or any errors or omissions in its content. \n <b>7</b>. Termination We reserve the right to terminate or suspend your access to the App at any time, without prior notice or liability, for any reason, including, but not limited to, a breach of these terms and conditions. \n <b>8</b>. Governing Law and Dispute Resolution These terms and conditions shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of [Jurisdiction]. Any disputes arising from or relating to the App or these terms shall be resolved through negotiation, and if necessary, through binding arbitration in accordance with the rules of [Arbitration Institution].</string>
</resources>